The crowd is cheering
lights are flashing gold
AI is rising
the future’s taking hold
No one’s crying
everyone’s saying “go”
But the wave is coming and it doesn’t know
résumé in perfect lines
AI’s faster, AI’s cheaper
So the door stays closed while my future retreats
attending every fair
I can’t outrun the algorithm
I can’t outlive the tide
I’m just one speck of dust in the river of time
I’m only human… and that’s still mine
I smile at my wife
I kiss my kids goodnight
position terminated tonight
Twenty years of loyalty
I set up a stall on the corner of the street
I’m learning new skills
I’m pretending tomorrow still belongs to me
I can’t outrun the algorithm
I can’t outlive the tide
I’m just one speck of dust in the river of time
You can take my work
I’m only human and that’s still mine
she only sees I’m tired
always believing I just need more time
the way we used to run
My friend knocks with sweets from the old school gate
Not the job they stole
the heart
The human thing no code can ever tear apart
I can’t outrun the algorithm
I can’t outlive the tide
You can take my work
somehow
'Cause we’ve got hearts and hearts don’t fade
and hearts don’t fade